criterion.com 2019-12-07

# The Criterion Collection

The Criterion Collection recognizes that visitors to our website care about the personal information that they provide us, and this privacy policy, part of our overall Terms and Conditions of Use, is intended to help you understand how we collect, store, and use the information we get from you (“personal information”).

**Information you provide**

When you purchase products from our website, sign up for our newsletter, or sign in as a registered user on our site, you may be asked to provide personal information such as your name, e-mail address, billing address, or credit card number. We only require the information we need to complete your request, and we only use that information as necessary to fulfill the requirements of the website, including, for example, processing your order, adding you to our e-mail lists, establishing you as a registered user of the site, resolving customer service or technical problems that affect your account, or giving access to personalized services of the site. We may also contact you from time to time with information we think is important to all of our users or customers. 

Some of the personal information you provide may be shared with third-party vendors who provide regular services to our website, such as our warehouse and fulfillment service, credit card authorization service, or e-mail newsletter application. We do use third-party vendor services such as Google Analytics to learn about how our site is being used, but we do not capture the personal information you provide to us in those programs. Our website does not receive or store credit card numbers, which are processed directly by our credit card authorization service, Stripe, Inc., whose privacy policy can be found on their website. 

We make reasonable efforts to ensure that any third-party contractor only uses the data we provide to perform the services we have contracted for and to protect the data at least as much as described in this policy. Although we may make reasonable inquiries to determine that such other organizations maintain website privacy policies comparable to ours, we are not responsible for the enforcement of such policies. 

**Cookies**

Like most websites, ours uses “cookies.” A “cookie” is a text file that we maintain on your hard drive that is invoked by your browser and enables us to recognize you when you visit the site and keep track of such things as your sign-in status and the items in your shopping cart. The information gathered in cookies is not made available to other organizations.

**Administration of our web site and compliance with law**

We may disclose or access account information for administrative and other purposes that we believe are necessary to develop, maintain, and improve our products and services. We also may disclose your personal information if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, a subpoena, or other legal process.

**You can review and change your personal information**

We encourage users to update and edit their personal information and keep it current by notifying us of any changes. In certain jurisdictions, such as the European Union, you may have a right to access, correct, port, or even erase the data we have about you. To make such a request, contact us at [mulvaney@criterion.com](mailto:mulvaney@criterion.com). You can also write to us at:

The Criterion Collection  
215 Park Avenue South  
New York, NY 10003  
Attn: Customer Service 

**Security used to protect your information**

We take commercially reasonable steps to maintain the security of customer information via a variety of access controls, including password protection, electronic firewalls, and data encryption. However, no mode of transmission or method of storage can be completely secure, so Criterion cannot guarantee the security of such information.

**Other organizations linked to our website**

We may provide links to other websites, but Criterion is not responsible for the privacy policies, terms and conditions of use, or content of those websites. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with the privacy policies and terms and conditions of use of linked websites. If you agree to provide information to such companies, that information will be subject to their privacy policies.

**Cross-Border Data Transfer**

Criterion is located in the United States. If you are visiting our website, setting up an account with us, or otherwise providing us with your information, you should know that your information will be processed in the United States, and the United States’ privacy laws may be different from the laws applicable where you are located. If you are located in the European Union, we process your data only to the extent needed to provide you the services or products you have purchased, including by administering your account with us and keeping you updated about events and news related to Criterion.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

Criterion may revise its privacy policy from time to time. We encourage you to visit this page periodically to review our current policy so that you will always know what information we gather and how we may use that information.

If you have any questions, please e-mail us at: [mulvaney@criterion.com](mailto:mulvaney@criterion.com)
